<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" ?>
<manuals>
    <manual title="man">
        <abstract>This manual explains the usage of the "man" command, how to read and interpret vCommand manuals and how to use related features.</abstract>
        
        <section title="Command Arguments">
            <body>The first argument to the command is a title or a regular expression.
If any manual has that exact title, it is instantly returned. (of course, assumming that the title is included in the lookup location)

Otherwise, the argument is treated as a regular exception and checked against different parts of the manual, determined by the flags documented in section 1.1.

If only part of a manual is needeed, such as title, abstract or index, other flags are available, documented in section 1.2.

A custom driver (section 2) can be specified using an argument documented in section 1.3.</body>
        
            <section title="Lookup Location Flags">
                <body>To allow more flexible lookups, man provides the choice of where to look at in a manual.
A set of flags which can be specified individually in parameters is used for this.

The overall set of flags must indicate at least one part to look at.

The following flags are available:
nomt - Exclude manual titles from lookup.
ma   - Include manual abstracts in lookup.
st   - Include section titles in lookup.
sb   - Include section bodies in lookup.</body>
            </section>
        
            <section title="Displayed Information Flags">
                <body>Should only part of a manual be needed, this can be requested through the presence of a flag.
Only one such flag may be present.
Their absence means the whole manual will be displayed using a driver.

The following flags are available:
jt - Just the title will be displayed.
ja - Just the abstract will be displayed.
ji - Just the index will be displayed.</body>
            </section>
        
            <section title="Extra Choices">
                <body>A few more arguments can be specified for extra choices.

    driver=
If an argument starting with "driver=" is specified, everything after it is used as a name or regular expression to find a driver.

    section=
If an argument starting with "section=" is specified, the body of the specified section will be outputted.
(Sub-)Sections are separated by a "." (dot).</body>
            </section>
        </section>
        
        <section title="Drivers">
            <body>A driver is in charge of displaying the manual to the user.
vCommands includes an output driver by default, which outputs the manual from the man command in an easily-readable way.

To find which drivers are available, the following command can be executed:
man . driver=.*
(note: the first . (dot) can be anything)
If this does not return error code 20 or 21, it means there is only one driver available.
An error code of 21 would also display all drivers' names. Error code 20 would mean there is no driver at all, rendering this command unable to display manuals.</body>
        </section>
        
        <section title="Status Codes">
            <body>The following are the status codes returned by the command and their meaning:

0   - No erroneous situation.

1   - Not enough arguments (at least one is required).
2   - First argument failed to evaluate.
3   - An argument (other than the first) failed to evaluate.
4   - More than one display information flag is present.
5   - Lookup location flags excluded all locations.

10  - No driver to display manual with (none specified and/or no default).
11  - No driver found matching given mask.
12  - More than one driver matches given mask.
13  - Nothing specified after "driver=".

20  - No manual found matching given mask with given lookup location(s).
21  - More than one manual matches given mask with given lookup location(s).

30  - Nothin specified after "section=".
31  - Specified section is not a set of number separated by dots.
32  - A section index is 0 or negative.
33  - A specified (sub-)section does not exist.</body>
        </section>
    </manual>
</manuals>